Uh, four "Under the Seas,"
two "Enchanted Evenings,"
and one "Night to Remember"
(Penny:)that... I cannot remember
for the life of me.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hey, where's
Bernadette?
(Howard:)She and Amy are out dress
shopping for their prom thing.
(Howard:)Oh, yeah,
I got that Evite.
Ever since I saw Pretty in Pink,
(Raj:)I've wanted to go
to an American prom.
But then I saw Carrie,
(Raj:)and I did not want to go
to an American prom.
(Raj:)But then I saw
Never Been Kissed,
(Raj:)and I'm back
on the prom bandwagon.
(Raj:)This prom thing's been
a real roller coaster.
(Howard:)Bernie's really excited.
I-I could tell because
her voice got so high,
(Howard:)the beagle next door
started howling.
(Raj:)Did you go to your prom?
(Leonard:)No.
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)I had a date
with a proper education.
(Sheldon:)Instead of a tuxedo,
I dressed myself in good habits.
(Sheldon:)Instead of spiked punch,
(Sheldon:)I enjoyed the intoxicating
flavor of knowledge.
(Sheldon:)Instead of
dancing in a gym,